ORIT LESHEM

050-4877577 | azmono@gmail.com

Profile

A motivating collaborative **General Manager** with over 15 years of experience in business management, 3 years in the health sector. Specializing in developing and mentoring leaders and team building. A strong financial acumen with Superior communication skills. I have a master's degree in Business management, experienced with creating strategies aligned with organizational plans. Creating measurable objectives strategies and designing action plans to support those plans. I was a volunteer EMT responder and Ambulance driver, with over 4 years serving the elderly population.

Work Experience

General Manager

January 2019 - January 2021

Kinneret-mall Shopping Center, Jordan Valley, Israel

- Managed 40 properties in a 26,000 square meter shopping center. Providing a commercially viable first-class shopping and gathering experience.
- Responsible for the day-to-day operation of the mall, providing top services and customed activities for specific target markets, including senior citizens lifestyle.
- Created and executed business strategy, raising shopping center appraisal value by 14.7% over two years.
- Annual operating and capital budgets execution, as well as forecasting of budget requirements and revisions as necessary to respond to changing market conditions.
- Management of department heads marketing, operations, events, accounting, legal and design.
 Personal coaching and mentoring of mangers, goals settings and development to fulfill goals.
- Building trusted vendor relationships.
- Quarterly reporting to the corporate board of directors Leading the marketing plan development, as well as ongoing reviews.
- Conducting tours of the malls' properties, to potential vendors, municipal authorities, Fire department and police. Negotiating lease contracts, payments and terms.
- Responsible for ensuring policies, programs, procedures and practices in each functional area.

Marketing Manager

January 2018 – December 2018

Kinneret-mall Shopping Center, Jordan Valley, Israel

- Created strategic marketing and sales plan, doubling tourists' busses traffic volume.
- Cultivated strong community partnerships, formed collaborations teaming with regional shopping groups, influencers, and opinion shapers.
- Developed website, marketing materials and unique concept to strengthen our local brand.
- Identified opportunities and created a local senior citizen "breakfast club", customized to senior citizen's needs, including activities, such as lectures, music events, market fairs.
- Production of public events, including music, festivals, gallery shows, and community events.
- Effectively used social media, print, radio, and digital mediums to increase shopping mall awareness. Increased Facebook likes by 20% in one year.

ORIT LESHEM

050-4877577 | azmono@gmail.com

Business Consultant / Development Manager

February 2009 – December 2017

Freelancer, Tel-Aviv, Israel

- Consulted for small and medium business. Manger's development Personal coaching and mentoring for mangers and business owners. Goals oriented management. Personal development to fulfill goals.
- Built and trained sales and support teams. Drafted contracts, and all professional manuals.

Service & Operations Manager, Nurses Call Center

January 2006 - January 2009

Clalit Health Services, Netanya Israel

Managed Clalit health services national call center, responsible for 120 nurses' team.

Education

Education	
SEI Software Engineering Immersive, Full Stack Developer	2021
General Assembly, Toronto, Canada	
Emergency Medical Responder (EMR) and Ambulance driver	2016
Certified US equivalent of Basic EMT, and Ambulance driver	
MBA Marketing and advertising specialization	2007
The college for management, Rishon-Lezion, Israel	
Canadian equivalency by WES: Master's degree	
Bachelor of business Marketing and HR specialization	2004
The college for management, Rishon-Lezion, Israel	
Canadian equivalency by WES: Bachelor's degree (four years)	
Awards	
Awarded the International Advertising Association's Diploma in Marketing Co	mmunications
The college for management Pishon-Lezion Israel	2007

The college for management, Rishon-Lezion, Israel 2007

Bachelor of business Graduated with honor - Magna cum Laude

The college for management, Rishon-Lezion, Israel

2004

Volunteer Experience

Emergency Medical Responder (EMR) and Ambulance driver

2016 - 2021

Israeli Red Cross first aid volunteer organization

- Ambulance driver, and medical responder.
- Serving mostly senior population and 3rd age nursing homes. Providing of first aid at client's location and evacuation to Hospital as necessary.
- Supervision of multi-participant events clinic such as a marathon run clinic.